<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="event.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>
<grotto

xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="SantaSchema.xsd">
    <xmas>
        <name>Santa</name>
        <overview>The Boss</overview>
        <statistics>
            <population type="approx"> Weight:200kg</population>
			
        </statistics>
        <era type="modern">
            <dateFrom> Working since:1900</dateFrom>
            <dateTo>Present</dateTo>
            <events>
                <event id="1">
                    <name> Santa's backround</name>
                    <image>SantaC.png</image>
                    <date>2012</date>
					
                    <bio>
                        <Story>Santa’s Story
                            Santa Claus is often described as a large man with a long white beard in scarlet robes lined with fur. 
                            He typified the spirit of good cheer at Christmas, bringing peace, joy, good food and wine and revelry. 
                            The Victorian revival of Christmas included Father Christmas as the emblem of 'good cheer'. 
                            His physical appearance was variable, with one famous image being John Leech's illustration of the "Ghost of Christmas Present" in Charles Dickens's festive classic A Christmas Carol (1843), as a great genial man in a green coat lined with fur who takes Scrooge through the bustling streets of London on the current Christmas morning, sprinkling the essence of Christmas onto the happy populace
                        </Story>
						
                        <etc/>
                    </bio>
                    <details>
                        <detail id="1">Lives in LapLand</detail>
                        <detail id="2">Delievers all over the world</detail>
                    </details>
                </event>
                <event id="2">
                    <name>His Reindeers</name>
                    <image>reindeer1.png</image>
					
                   
                    <bio>
                        <Story>when, what to to my wondering eyes should appear,
                            but a miniature sleigh, and eight tiny rein-deer,
                            with a little old driver, so lively and quick,
                            I knew in a moment it must be St. Nick.

                            More rapid than eagles his coursers they came,
                            And he whistled, and shouted, and call'd them by name:
                            "Now, Dasher! Now, Dancer! Now, Prancer, and Vixen!
                            "On, Comet! On, Cupid! On, Donder and Blitzen!

                            "To the top of the porch! to the top of the wall!
                            "Now dash away! dash away! dash away all!"
                            As dry leaves that before the wild hurricane fly,
                            When they meet with an obstacle, mount to the sky;
                            So up to the house-top the coursers they flew,
                        </Story>
                        
                        <etc/>
                    </bio>
                    <details>
                        <detail id="1">The Reindeer's
                            Rudolf
                            Dasher 
                            Dancer 
                            Prancer 
                            Vixen
                            Comet 
                            Cupid 
                            Donner 
                            Blitz-en
                        </detail>
                    </details>
                </event>
            </events>
        </era>
    </xmas>
    <xmas>
        <name>Rudolf</name>
        <overview>BADDEST REINDDER OF THEM ALL</overview>
        <statistics>
            <population type="approx"></population>
            
            <etc/>
        </statistics>
        <era type="modern">
            <dateFrom>Working since:1900</dateFrom>
            <dateTo>Present</dateTo>
            <events>
                <event id="1">
                    <name>The Main reindeer</name>
                    <image>rudolph.png</image>
                    <date>1906</date>
                   
                    <bio>
                        <Story>Rudolf is a reindeer with a glowing red nose, popularly known as "Santa's 9th Reindeer." When depicted, he is the lead reindeer pulling Santa's sleigh on Christmas Eve.
                              The luminosity of his nose is so great that it illuminates the team's path through inclement winter weather.
                        </Story>
                    </bio>
                    <details>
                        <detail id="1">Top reindeer, all round buzzer.</detail>
                    </details>
                </event>
            </events>
        </era>
    </xmas>
</grotto>